DOMINIC WEISS

Energetic and Highly Motivated Business Professional

Las Vegas, NV 89169 dom.k.weiss.1@gmail.com (702) 234-0820

Energetic and highly motivated business professional, with 5+ years in B2B, B2C, and marketing, and customer service. There is nothing you can throw my way that I can't handle. Enthusiastic leader, and employee with a passion for providing excellent customer service, and ensuring recurring business.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Server

Favorite Bistro

April 2019 to Present

- Energetic, goal-focused leader with a genuine interest in providing great customer service as well as providing a hand to help those on my team also execute their job flawlessly.
- The ability to lead others, take care of the customer, and up-sell the consumer to increase company profits, while maintaining a professional appearance, and keep an above 90 % customer satisfaction rate.

Front Line Sales - Timeshare

Wyndham Destinations - Las Vegas, NV December 2018 to April 2019

- Presented professional appearance at all times.
- Built strong, professional relationships through the identification of client needs, which increased overall sales and opportunities.
- Negotiated and closed deals with minimal oversight.

Executive Assistant

Motion Corp - Las Vegas, NV December 2015 to November 2018

Worked with CEO/ CFO to resolve company problems, improve operations and provide exceptional customer service.

• Overlooked real estate, and restaurant operations.

• Maintained a professional record of constantly getting the job done, as effectively and quickly as possible.

Political Canvasser (Concurrent with Executive Assistant)

Motion Corp - Las Vegas, NV August 2018 to October 2018

- Developed lists of potential areas and neighborhoods to increase success rates for the State Assembly, and State Senate.
- Promoted the State Assembly, and State Senate over the phone, digitally, and by canvassing residential neighborhoods.
- Actively enticed new member by using persuasive and effective marketing // sales tactics.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Business Management

Northern Arizona University

SKILLS

- B2B Sales
- B2C Sales
- Verbal / Non-Verbal Communication
- Digital Literacy
- Leadership
- Customer Service
- Time Management
- Negotiation
- Personal Assistant Experience
- Sales Management
- Business Development
- Marketing

LINKS

http://linkedin.com/in/dominic-weiss-5ab7131a9

CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

CPR

Real Estate / TimeShare	
Event Management	
Overcoming Objections	
Sales Closing Strategies	
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION	

Volunteer Work

- Haiti Mission
- Mexico Mission
- Benjamin Carson Foundation
- Salvation Army Red Cross